day 11 good day guys
hi all right
good morning
washed yesterday Dude
second guys
bora do the job
this showcase is dirty eh
tell me I give you you're out of money
doesn't pick a lot of guys
take the opportunity that has to appear
and then yes
halfway through the path you go there
make your money
and then you direct it to what you want
is on
don't just stand there waiting for the deal to happen
go to crazy street
get a soap
1 old wheel and you'll be able to make 1 money Dude
taking a few no shovels
here is also part
it's on let's go
caraca hand
look how many chair
ok bye bye
thank you worth
come tomorrow bro
it didn't take long
I have a new product that we ask for
take the bacteria out of the chair
old I'm off duty today
but then there's 1 boy cutting and 1 father lying there
and look here also at these details
oh and it wouldn't be with me friend
with my boss
I step after
thank you
goodbye good morning
I come after
there another hour there beauty
tamo together
and then troop
it was worth the hour
look
my fingers
ugly tail
no bro
I canceled a client here because of back pain
old Chevrolet seat is broken
I've been sleeping crookedly for about three days now
but the pain today began to take a turn
it wasn't like that no
and then I started making the windows
thinking that
it was going to get better for the body to warm up and then it got worse
know how much the daily is
they are for you and there are a hundred reais in a pix does not give a discount
no no TV
bed has
bathroom has yes
girl beauty
all good for you
bye bye a hundred tale doesn't give no bro
one night is very expensive old man
now i'm going to one where the woman gave me the address
but I don't think so at all
this street is like this o
I climb one and turn right
valeu valeu
thanks bro
good aunt good sings a lot and still has to unfold
I didn't post a place for me to stay
because i'm jumping from
place in place
that's what you have for today
tomorrow i think i'll invest in something that
might change the game